<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[KumaaaR KonnecT...]]></title>
  <link href="http://kumar1541.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://kumar1541.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-04T16:35:40+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://kumar1541.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[kum@r_deep@k]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are smart phones Really That Smart !!!! ]]></title>
    <link href="http://kumar1541.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/are-smart-phones-really-that-smart/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T14:36:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://kumar1541.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/are-smart-phones-really-that-smart</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A smartphone is a mobile phone built on a mobile operating system, with more advanced computing capability and connectivity than a feature phone.</p>

<p>[1]</p>

<pre><code>The first smartphones combined the functions of a personal digital assistant (PDA) with a mobile phone. 
</code></pre>

<p>[2]</p>

<pre><code>Later models added the functionality of portable media players, low-end compact digital cameras, pocket video cameras, and GPS navigation
units to form one multi-use device. Many modern smartphones also include high-resolution touchscreens and web browsers that display
standard web pages as well as mobile-optimized sites. High-speed data access is provided by Wi-Fi and mobile broadband. 
</code></pre>

<p>[3]</p>

<pre><code>In recent years, the rapid development of mobile app markets and of mobile commerce have been drivers of smartphone adoption.


          'Operating Systems Market'



   The mobile operating systems (OS) used by modern smartphones include 
   Google's Android, Apple's iOS, Nokia's Symbian, RIM's BlackBerry OS, Samsung's Bada, Microsoft's Windows Phone, Hewlett-Packard's
   webOS, and embedded Linux distributions such as Maemo and MeeGo. 

   Such operating systems can be installed on many different phone models, and typically each device can receive multiple OS software
   updates over its lifetime. 

   A few other upcoming operating systems are Mozilla's Firefox OS, Canonical Ltd.'s Ubuntu Phone, and Tizen.
</code></pre>

<p>   As of now , major OS are in market which are strong competeters listing as</p>

<pre><code>   Android
   Windows
   Apple iOS
</code></pre>

<p>   All these mainly contributing high end device which is possibly not for every group of people to afford.
   Rest of the OS contributes to the low end devices and ofcourse larger part of the market.</p>

<p><img src="http://cdn.ndtv.com/tech/images/gadgets/ubuntu-phone-635.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
